Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is pumpkin cheesecake. And can we
just take a second to appreciate how
thick this thing is? It kind of reminds
me of your mom. Let me show you how to
make it. We're starting off with 400 g
of a fat-free, high protein milk,
followed by some vanilla bean paste,
sweetener, salt, zanthan gum, and some
pumpkin pie spice. Then we're going to
do a little bit of pumpkin and finish it
off with some cream cheese. Also guys, I
think I made the switch to the immersion
blender all time. It blends these pints
way better than a hand frozen. After
everything's combined, you can throw it
in the freezer for at least 16 hours.
Take it out, run it under hot water for
about a minute, and then throw it in
your creamy on the light ice cream
setting. Since we used a decent amount
of fat in this recipe, you should only
need one spin, but of course, respin if
it comes out crumbly. And just look at
the texture of this thing. Adding cream
cheese is kind of a hack to getting some
super thick, dense ice cream. And to
finish it off, we'll just top it with
some crumbled graham cracker. And then
you have Ben & Jerry's pumpkin
cheesecake ice cream for a quarter of
the